Me you we’re gonna leave here
Me you kita berusaha meninggalkan tempat ini
Me you 僕らはここを離れようとしている
Me you, vamos a irnos de aquí
Me you พวกเราจะจากที่แห่งนี้ไป
Me you 我们想要离开这里
Me you chúng ta sẽ sớm rời khỏi nơi đây
Hop on quickly our hearts are at same place
Cepat naik, hati kita di tempat yang sama
早く乗り込んで 心は同じ所に
Súbete rápido, el corazón sigue en el mismo lugar
รีบขึ้นมาเร็ว หัวใจของเราอยู่ด้วยกัน
快上来 心向着同一个地方
Lên cao thật nhanh, đến nơi trái tim ta đồng điệu
Worry about small problems maybe next time
Kegelisahan yang tak perlu itu lakukan saja lain kali
たかがそんな悩みは 今度にして
Súbete rápido, el corazón sigue en el mismo lugar
เรื่องกังวลเหล่านั้น เก็บเอาไว้คิดทีหลัง
先把烦恼抛之脑后吧
để những lo lắng ấy lại phía sau
We’re running out of time so now we on our way
Kita sudah tak punya waktu so now we on our way
時間が足りないから so now we on our way
No hay tiempo, so now we on our wayy
เราไม่มีเวลาแล้วนะ so now we on our way
时间紧迫 so now we on our way
Không còn nhiều thời gian mà so now we on our way
Freely come join me
Dengan bebas come join me
自由に come join me
Libremente, come join me
มีอิสระเสรี come join me
自由地 come join me
một cách tự do come join me
I show my dream on the surface
Bisakah kau lihat mimpiku yang muncul di atas air
水面の上で夢を広げてみるよ
Mostramos nuestro sueño sobre el agua
แสดงความฝันบนผิวน้ำให้ดู
在水面上 展开梦想
bạn có thấy ước mơ đang sải cánh trên mặt nước
It has begun, the story like a movie
Sudah dimulai, cerita bagai film
始まった 映画のようなストーリー
Ha empezado una historia como una película
เรื่องราวที่เหมือนกับภาพยนตร์ได้เริ่มขึ้นแล้ว
开始了 如电影般的故事
bắt đầu rồi đó, một câu chuyện tựa như trong phim
I can do this all day all day long
I can do this all day sepanjang hari
I can do this all day 一日中
I can do this all day, todo el día
I can do this all day ตลอดทั้งวัน
I can do this all day 一整天
I can do this all day, suốt ngày dài
we got this today too
We got this hari ini juga di sini
we got this 今日もここは
we got this, hoy también
we got this ที่แห่งนี้ในวันนี้
we got this 今天这里
we got this cũng là hôm nay, cũng tại nơi đây
We take this place 100%
Kita kuasai 100%
僕らが占領する 100%
Ocupamos este lugar, 100%
พวกเราจะครอบครองมัน 100%
由我们占据 100%
chúng ta đã chiếm được 100%
Move on to the next level higher mental
Ke level selanjutnya higher mental
超えていく 次の段階 higher mental
Pasemos al siguiente paso, higher mental
ไปยังขั้นต่อไป higher mental
开启下一阶段 higher mental
bước lên một bậc cao hơn higher mental
We’re already on another level another level ya
Kita sudah ada di level lain, berbeda level ya
僕らはすでに違う次元 違う level ya
Ya estamos en otra dimensión, otro level ya
ระดับของพวกเรานั้นต่างกับคนอื่น คนละ level ya
我们已经到达不同层面 不同level ya
chúng ta đã ở một tầm cao khác một level khác ya
let’s start we gon’ fly
we won’t stop it’s alright
I can do this all day
back it up back it up
Hurry up ‘hit that line’
Cepatlah 'hit that line'
急いで ‘hit that line’
Date prisa, ‘hit that line’
ต้องรีบแล้วล่ะ ‘hit that line’
抓紧时间 ‘hit that line’
Khẩn trương lên, 'hit that line'
It’s a waste of time (you should)
Waktu terbuang (you should)
時間がもったいない もったいない(you should)
Corre el tiempo, que corre (you should)
เสียดาย เสียดายเวลา (you should)
时间紧迫 紧迫 (you should)
Thật phí thời gian (you should)
I don’t need no more sign ya
Tidak perlu no more sign ya
要らない no more sign ya
No hace falta, no more sign ya
ไม่ต้องการอะไรอีกแล้ว no more sign ya
不需要 no more sign ya
Chẳng cần thêm no more sign ya
Wherever you are I can find ya
Di manapun kau berada I can find ya
君がどこにいても I can find ya
Estés donde estés, I can find ya
ไม่ว่าคุณจะอยู่ที่ใด I can find ya
不论你在何处 I can find ya
dù bạn đang nơi đâu I can find ya
it’s gonna be alright
Put the hands together make a wish
Tangkupkan tangan make a wish
手を合わせて make a wish
Junta las manos, make a wish
ประสานมือไว้ make a wish
双手合十 make a wish
nắm chặt tay make a wish
hoo you should
make a wish
I’ll take you anywhere
(let me do it for you)
never stop keep breaking out
still working all the time
We gotta get out of here
Kita akan keluar dari sini we gon' fly away
抜け出さなきゃ
Tenemos que escaparnos
เราต้องออกไปจากที่นี่
勇敢摆脱
phải rời khởi đây
we gon’ fly away
Buka mata lebar-lebar dan mimpikanlah (mimpi)
With eyes wide open, we have a (dream)
Di tempat masing-masing kita menghirup (napas)
目をしっかり開けて夢を(見る)
Con los ojos bien abiertos (sueña)
ลืมตาให้กว้าง และใฝ่ฝัน (ฝัน)
睁大眼睛做梦
Ngước mắt thật cao và mơ thật lớn
In each position we take a (breath)
それぞれの場所で私たちは息を(する)
En el lugar de cada uno (respiramos)
พวกเราหายใจ อยู่ในที่ของเรา (หายใจ)
我们在各自的位置上呼吸
Hít thở một hơi nơi không gian của riêng mình
If we’re connected you’re already a (star)
Jika kita terhubung kau juga sudah jadi (star)
僕ら通じあっていれば君も既に(star)
Si nos entendemos, es que ya eres una (star)
ถ้าพวกเราเข้าใจกัน คุณก็คือ (star)
如果我们心灵相通 你已经是(star)
Nếu chúng ta đồng điệu, bạn vốn đã là (star)
(You’re already a star)
(Kau juga sudah jadi star)
(君も既にstar)
(Ya eres una star)
(คุณก็คือ star)
(你已经是star)
(Bạn vốn đã là star)
I don’t get exhausted got no limit
Tanpa lelah got no limit
疲れない got no limit
No nos cansamos, got no limit
ฉันไม่เหนื่อยหรอก got no limit
不知疲惫 got no limit
Không hề mệt mỏi got no limit
My heart pounds keep drumming
Jantung berdebar keep drumming
心臓はドンドン keep drumming
El corazón bumbum, keep drumming
หัวใจเต้นแรง keep drumming
心脏砰砰 keep drumming
Tim thình thịch keep drumming
Pour the whole barrel of oil
Menuang seluruh isi jerigen minyak
全て注いでしまえ 油
Derrama toda la cuba de gasolina
เทน้ำมันถังนั้นออกมาให้หมด
整桶油都倒进去
Xăng đầy bình
I’m ready to ride right now
I'm ready to ride langsung sekarang
I’m ready to ride 今すぐ
I'm ready to ride, ahora mismo
I’m ready to ride ตอนนี้เลย
I’m ready to ride 就是现在
I’m ready to ride ngay bây giờ
let’s start we gon’ fly
we won’t stop it’s alright
I can do this all day
back it up back it up
Hurry up ‘hit that line’
Cepatlah 'hit that line'
急いで ‘hit that line’
Date prisa, ‘hit that line’
ต้องรีบแล้วล่ะ ‘hit that line’
抓紧时间 ‘hit that line’
Khẩn trương lên, 'hit that line'
It’s a waste of time (you should)
Waktu terbuang (you should)
時間がもったいない もったいない(you should)
Corre el tiempo, que corre (you should)
เสียดาย เสียดายเวลา (you should)
时间紧迫 紧迫 (you should)
Thật phí thời gian (you should)
I don’t need no more sign ya
Tidak perlu no more sign ya
要らない no more sign ya
No hace falta, no more sign ya
ไม่ต้องการอะไรอีกแล้ว no more sign ya
不需要 no more sign ya
Chẳng cần thêm no more sign ya
Wherever you are I can find ya
Di manapun kau berada I can find ya
君がどこにいても I can find ya
Estés donde estés, I can find ya
ไม่ว่าคุณจะอยู่ที่ใด I can find ya
不论你在何处 I can find ya
dù bạn đang nơi đâu I can find ya
it’s gonna be alright
Put the hands together make a wish
Tangkupkan tangan make a wish
手を合わせて make a wish
Junta las manos, make a wish
ประสานมือไว้ make a wish
双手合十 make a wish
nắm chặt tay make a wish
Your energy it links me up (links me up)
Energimu it links me up (links me up)
君のエネルギー it links me up (links me up)
Mi energía, it links me up (links me up)
พลังของคุณ it links me up (links me up)
你的能量 it links me up (links me up)
năng lượng của bạn it links me up (links me up)
Feel this feeling now (I’ll do it for you)
Sekarang coba rasakan ini (I’ll do it for you)
今この気持ちを感じてみて (I’ll do it for you)
Siente esta sensación (I’ll do it for you)
ลองสัมผัสความรู้สึกนี้ดูสิ (I’ll do it for you)
感受一下 现在的心情吧 (I’ll do it for you)
hãy cảm nhận cảm giác này ngay bây giờ (I’ll do it for you)
I can take you anywhere
Aku bisa mengantarmu ke manapun
君をどこにだって連れていける
Puedo llevarte a cualquier sitio
ฉันสามารถพาคุณไปได้ทุกที่
可以带你去任何地方
tôi sẽ đưa bạn đến bất kì đâu
(I’m getting closer to you)
(Perlahan mendekat padamu)
(少しずつ君に行く)
(Paso a paso me acerco a ti)
(ฉันจะเข้าใกล้คุณทีละนิด)
(慢慢向你靠近)
(lại gần bạn thêm từng chút một)
Don’t worry let go
Jangan khawatir let go
心配しないで let go
Sin preocupaciones, let go
ไม่ต้องกังวลไป let go
不要担心 let go
đừng lo lắng let go
Put the hands together put the hands together
Tangkupkan tangan tangkupkan tangan
手を合わせて 手を合わせて
Junta las manos, junta las manos
ประสานมือไว้ ประสานมือไว้
双手合十 双手合十
nắm chặt tay nắm chặt tay
now make a wish
I can do this all day
(I don't need to answer
don't need a question
we no professor) oh oh oh
that I want
Put the hands together put the hands together
Tangkupkan tangan tangkupkan tangan
手を合わせて 手を合わせて
(Junta las manos, junta las manos)
ประสานมือไว้ ประสานมือไว้
双手合十 双手合十
nắm chặt tay nắm chặt tay
now make a wish
I don’t need no more sign ya
Tidak perlu no more sign ya
要らない no more sign ya
No hace falta, no more sign ya
ไม่ต้องการอะไรอีกแล้ว no more sign ya
不需要 no more sign ya
Chẳng cần thêm no more sign ya
Wherever you are I can find ya
Di manapun kau berada I can find ya
君がどこにいても I can find ya
Estés donde estés, I can find ya
ไม่ว่าคุณจะอยู่ที่ใด I can find ya
不论你在何处 I can find ya
dù bạn đang nơi đâu I can find ya
it’s gonna be alright
Put the hands together make a wish
Tangkupkan tangan make a wish
手を合わせて make a wish
Junta las manos, make a wish
ประสานมือไว้ make a wish
双手合十 make a wish
nắm chặt tay make a wish
I can do this all day
back it up back it up
Hurry up ‘hit that line’
Cepatlah 'hit that line'
急いで ‘hit that line’
Date prisa, ‘hit that line’
ต้องรีบแล้วล่ะ ‘hit that line’
抓紧时间 ‘hit that line’
Khẩn trương lên, 'hit that line'
It’s a waste of time (you should)
Waktu terbuang (you should)
時間がもったいない もったいない(you should)
Corre el tiempo, que corre (you should)
เสียดาย เสียดายเวลา (you should)
时间紧迫 紧迫 (you should)
Thật phí thời gian (you should)
I don’t need no more sign ya
Tidak perlu no more sign ya
要らない no more sign ya
No hace falta, no more sign ya
ไม่ต้องการอะไรอีกแล้ว no more sign ya
不需要 no more sign ya
Chẳng cần thêm no more sign ya
Wherever you are I can find ya
Di manapun kau berada I can find ya
君がどこにいても I can find ya
Estés donde estés, I can find ya
ไม่ว่าคุณจะอยู่ที่ใด I can find ya
不论你在何处 I can find ya
dù bạn đang nơi đâu I can find ya
it’s gonna be alright
Put the hands together make a wish
Tangkupkan tangan make a wish
手を合わせて make a wish
Junta las manos, make a wish
ประสานมือไว้ make a wish
双手合十 make a wish
nắm chặt tay make a wish
make a wish
(it’s your birthday it’s your)
(I’ll give you birthday cake yea)
make a wish
it’s gonna be alright
(Put the hands together put the hands together)
(Tangkupkan tangan tangkupkan tangan)
(手を合わせて 手を合わせて)
(Junta las manos, junta las manos)
(ประสานมือไว้ ประสานมือไว้)
(双手合十 双手合十)
(nắm chặt tay nắm chặt tay)
(Put the hands together put the hands together now)
(Tangkupkan tangan tangkupkan tangan now)
(手を合わせて 手を合わせて now)
(Junta las manos, junta las manos, now)
(ประสานมือไว้ ประสานมือไว้ now)
(双手合十 双手合十 now)
(nắm chặt tay nắm chặt tay now)
make a wish